A Guide to the Policy Office Legislative Files of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
- HB 948 (00) Juvenile community crime control act (Box 31, Folder 85)
- HB 949 (00) Bonds of fiduciaries, trustees, guardians or estate administrators (Box 31, Folder 86)
- HB 951 (00) Purchase of surplus materials by children's homes (Box 31, Folder 87)
- HB 953 (00) Claims against counties (Box 31, Folder 88)
- HB 959 (00) Solid waste management; permits (Box 31, Folder 89)
- HB 961 (00) State health care plan; additional coverage for retired state employees (Box 31, Folder 90)
- HB 967 (00) City street maintenance payments (Box 31, Folder 91)
- HB 973 (00) Local retail farmers markets (Box 31, Folder 92)
- HB 975 (00) Remediation program regulations (Box 31, Folder 93)
- HB 977 (00) Election laws; absentee ballot procedures (Box 31, Folder 94)
- HB 978 (00) Punishment for conviction of felony (Box 31, Folder 95)
- HB 979 (00) Health professions; physician assistants (Box 31, Folder 96)
- HB 980 (00) Grants for tuition for certain education students (Box 31, Folder 97)
- HB 981 (00) Solid waste management facilities (Box 31, Folder 98)
- HB 982 (00) HIV premium assistance program (Box 31, Folder 99)
- HB 983 (00) Health; immunizations and certificates (Box 31, Folder 100)
- HB 985 (00) Corrections; guards to be same gender (Box 31, Folder 101)
- HB 987 (00) Transfer of credits for private school students (Box 31, Folder 102)
- HB 988 (00) Vision impaired; board and department (Box 31, Folder 103)
- HB 991 (00) VASAP to monitor certain restricted licenses (Box 31, Folder 104)
- HB 994 (00) Veterinarians; release of immunization information (Box 31, Folder 105)
- HB 999 (00) Salvage vehicle; release of motor vehicle information (Box 31, Folder 106)
- HB 1002 (00) Vehicle registration; taxicabs (Box 31, Folder 107)
- HB 1004 (00) Prisoners' alternative sentencing programs (Box 31, Folder 108)
- HB 1005 (00) Freedom of information; exemptions (Box 31, Folder 109)
- HB 1007 (00) Workers' compensation; hazardous materials response team members (Box 31, Folder 110)
- HB 1008 (00) Return of bodies donated for scientific study (Box 31, Folder 111)
- HB 1009 (00) Education; western Virginia public education consortium (Box 31, Folder 112)
- HB 1010 (00) Student possession and self-administration of asthma medications (Box 31, Folder 113)
- HB 1011 (00 Medical students; service in medically underserved areas (Box 32, Folder 1)
- HB 1012 (00) Statewide asthma management (Box 32, Folder 2)
- HB 1013 (00) Drug control act; changes in practice of pharmacy (Box 32, Folder 3)
- HB 1014 (00) Health insurance; eligibility for medicare risk plans (Box 32, Folder 4)
- HB 1018 (00) Liability for failure to provide security or crowd control (Box 32, Folder 5)
- HB 1019 (00) Release of standards of learning assessments (Box 32, Folder 6)
- HB 1020 (00) Standards of learning assessments; social studies (Box 32, Folder 7)
- HB 1022 (00) Financial assurance for waste facilities (Box 32, Folder 8)
- HB 1023 (00) Financial responsibility for solid waste management facilities (Box 32, Folder 9)
- HB 1030 (00) Local fire marshals; police powers (Box 32, Folder 10)
- HB 1034 (00) Office of the inspector general for MHMRSAS (Box 32, Folder 11)
- HB 1036 (00) Workers' compensation; coverage for alien workers (Box 32, Folder 12)
- HB 1037 (00) Cotton handlers (Box 32, Folder 13)
- HB 1038 (00) Farmers markets (Box 32, Folder 14)
- HB 1046 (00) Procurement Act; thresholds for small purchases and contracts (Box 32, Folder 15)
- HB 1047 (00) Procurement act; architectural or professional engineering services (Box 32, Folder 16)
- HB 1048 (00) Small business growth fund (Box 32, Folder 17)
- HB 1049 (00) Registration of automated external defibrillators; immunity (Box 32, Folder 18)
- HB 1051 (00) Adult care residences (Box 32, Folder 19)
- HB 1057 (00) Enterprise zone act (Box 32, Folder 20)
- HB 1060 (00) Trustees as registered agent; partnerships and liability companies (Box 32, Folder 21)
- HB 1065 (00) Department of planning and budget; performance budgeting (Box 32, Folder 22)
- HB 1069 (00) Campaign finance disclosure act; campaign depositories (Box 32, Folder 23)
- HB 1075 (00) Dentist loan repayment program (Box 32, Folder 24)
- HB 1076 (00) Health workforce recruitment and retention; study report (Box 32, Folder 25)
- HB 1077 (00) Statewide cancer registry; civil penalties (Box 32, Folder 26)
- HB 1078 (00) Annual mixed beverage amphitheater licenses (Box 32, Folder 27)
- HB 1080 (00) Restoration of voting and civil rights to convicted felons (Box 32, Folder 28)
- HB 1086 (00) Solar photovoltaic manufacturing incentive grant program (Box 32, Folder 29)
- HB 1087 (00) Eula W. Radcliffe Memorial highway (Box 32, Folder 30)
- HB 1088 (00) Building code; farm buildings and structures (Box 32, Folder 31)
- HB 1090 (00) Organ donations (Box 32, Folder 32)
- HB 1091 (00) Outdoor advertising (Box 32, Folder 33)
- HB 1092 (00) Campaign finance disclosure (Box 32, Folder 34)
- HB 1093 (00) Alcoholic beverage control; farm winery licenses (Box 32, Folder 35)
- HB 1094 (00) Sales and use tax; modular building partial exclusion (Box 32, Folder 36)
- HB 1095 (00) Lease of Smith Mountain Lake (Box 32, Folder 37)
- HB 1096 (00) Local vehicle licenses and taxes (Box 32, Folder 38)
- HB 1097 (00) Criminal history record check; Floyd County public schools (Box 32, Folder 39)
- HB 1101 (00) Prepayable Fines (Box 32, Folder 40)
- HB 1102 (00) Alcohol safety action programs (Box 32, Folder 41)
- HB 1106 (00) Definition of "Criminal Justice Agency" (Box 32, Folder 42)
- HB 1108 (00) Body-piercing (Box 32, Folder 43)
- HB 1111 (00) Prescription drug formularies (Box 32, Folder 44)
- HB 1114 (00) Tourist train development authority (Box 32, Folder 45)
- HB 1123 (00) Transportation Commissioner: eminent domain (Box 32, Folder 46)
- HB 1124 (00) Legal holidays (Box 32, Folder 47)
- HB 1125 (00) Labor and employment; polygraphs (Box 32, Folder 48)
- HB 1126 (00) Disclosure of certain employment information (Box 32, Folder 49)
- HB 1128 (00) Appeals in abuse and neglect cases (Box 32, Folder 50)
- HB 1131 (00) Ignition interlock system (Box 32, Folder 50)
- HB 1133 (00) UVA's College at Wise; receipt of certain property (Box 32, Folder 52)
- HB 1134 (00) Electric utility consumption tax; costs incurred by cooperatives (Box 32, Folder 53)
- HB 1135 (00) Coal employment and production incentive tax credit (Box 32, Folder 54)
- HB 1136 (00) Campaign finance disclosure act; reports of contributions, etc. (Box 32, Folder 55)
- HB 1141 (00) Political campaign telephone calls; disclosure requirements (Box 32, Folder 56)
- HB 1142 (00) Income tax; rent reductions tax credit (Box 32, Folder 57)
- HB 1147 (00) Parental responsibility for student behavior (Box 32, Folder 58)
- HB 1150 (00) Shared custody (Box 32, Folder 59)
- HB 1152 (00) Campaign advertisements; identification requirements (Box 32, Folder 60)
- HB 1156 (00) Where forgery may be prosecuted (Box 32, Folder 61)
- HB 1159 (00) Composition of Board of visitors of Norfolk State University (Box 32, Folder 62)
- HB 1160 (00) Fees collected for court reporter fund (Box 32, Folder 63)
- HB 1162 (00 Racing commission; powers; live racing days (Box 32, Folder 63)
- HB 1163 (00) Charitable gaming commission; member expenses, notice of meetings, etc. (Box 32, Folder 65)
- HB 1164 (00) Land conservation foundation (Box 32, Folder 66)
- HB 1165 (00) Freedom of Information Act; record exemptions (Box 32, Folder 67)
- HB 1168 (00) Adult protective services; mandatory reporters (Box 32, Folder 68)
- HB 1169 (00) Adult protective services (Box 32, Folder 69)
- HB 1170 (00) Wetlands (Box 32, Folder 70)
- HB 1172 (00) U.S. Route 29 corridor development fund (Box 32, Folder 71)
- HB 1173 (00) Historic rehabilitation tax (Box 32, Folder 72)
- HB 1176 (00) Standardization prescription benefit cards or other technologies (Box 32, Folder 73)
- HB 1177 (00) Department of employee relations counselors; grievance procedure (Box 32, Folder 74)
- HB 1178 (00) Parent education (Box 32, Folder 75)
- HB 1181 (00) Board of Transportation safety (Box 32, Folder 76)
- HB 1184 (00) Action for damage to memorials for War Veterans (Box 32, Folder 77)
- HB 1186 (00) Commercial vehicles; use of certain lanes on interstate highways (Box 32, Folder 78)
- HB 1187 (00) FOIA; records exemption for attorney general (Box 32, Folder 79)
- HB 1192 (00) Maritime incident response advisory committee (Box 32, Folder 80)
- HB 1194 (00) Adult care residences; training (Box 32, Folder 81)
- HB 1196 (00) Accreditation, other standards and evaluation (Box 32, Folder 82)
- HB 1198 (00) Health professions; innovative pharmacy programs (Box 32, Folder 83)
- HB 1199 (00) Department for the aging toll-free hotline (Box 32, Folder 84)
- HB 1200 (00) Grant program for respite care services (Box 32, Folder 85)
- HB 1202 (00) Health; statewide AHEC program (Box 32, Folder 86)
- HB 1203 (00) Health care date reporting (Box 32, Folder 87)
- HB 1204 (00) Uniform commercial code; secured transactions (Box 32, Folder 88)
- HB 1205 (00) Writs on judgments for specific property (Box 32, Folder 89)
- HB 1206 (00) Juveniles; fingerprints and photographs (Box 32, Folder 90)
- HB 1207 (00) Priority of certain refinance mortgages over subordinate mortgages (Box 32, Folder 91)
- HB 1209 (00) Procurement act; protest of awards (Box 32, Folder 92)
- HB 1211 (00) Health maintenance organizations; exception to license requirement (Box 32, Folder 93)
- HB 1212 (00) School property; schools may permit use thereof (Box 32, Folder 94)
- HB 1213 (00) Summonses issued by attorneys; bar association to study effectivenessz (Box 32, Folder 95)
- HB 1214 (00) Solicitation of contributions act; enforcement (Box 32, Folder 96)
- HB 1216 (00) Sale of real estate for delinquent taxes; process (Box 33, Folder 1)
- HB 1219 (00) Secrecy of tax information (Box 33, Folder 2)
- HB 1223 (00) Outdoor advertising (Box 33, Folder 3)
- HB 1228 (00) Landfill closure (Box 33, Folder 4)
- HB 1229 (00) Assault and battery; actions by school personnel (Box 33, Folder 5)
- HB 1231 (00) Property owners' association act; access to records (Box 33, Folder 6)
- HB 1232 (00) Urban public-private partnership redevelopment fund (Box 33, Folder 7)
- HB 1233 (00) Procurement act; declaration of purpose (Box 33, Folder 8)
- HB 1236 (00) Refunds of unearned health insurance premiums (Box 33, Folder 9)
- HB 1238 (00) School boards; criminal records checks of employees (Box 33, Folder 10)
- HB 1239 (00) Procurement act; multiple awards (Box 33, Folder 11)
- HB 1240 (00) Procurement act; definitions; best value (Box 33, Folder 12)
- HB 1245 (00) Agricultural and forestal districts (Box 33, Folder 13)
- HB 1247 (00) Personal property tax; extension of time to pay (Box 33, Folder 14)
- HB 1249 (00) Nursing workforce information (Box 33, Folder 15)
- HB 1250 (00) Practice of acupuncture (Box 33, Folder 16)
- HB 1251 (00) Adult care residences; revised definitions (Box 33, Folder 17)
- HB 1255 (00) Advertisement of legal notices on web sites (Box 33, Folder 18)
- HB 1256 (00) Driver training schools (Box 33, Folder 19)
- HB 1257 (00) Organ and tissue donor registry (Box 33, Folder 20)
- HB 1262 (00) Local personnel systems (Box 33, Folder 21)
- HB 1266 (00) Health insurance; EDI standards for uniform referral form (Box 33, Folder 22)
- HB 1268 (00) Governor's economic development grant program (Box 33, Folder 23)
- HB 1269 (00) Liability for defamatory material on the internet (Box 33, Folder 24)
- HB 1270 (00) Certificate of public need (Box 33, Folder 25)
- HB 1271 (00) Workers' compensation; professional employer organizations (Box 33, Folder 26)
- HB 1275 (00) Fuels tax; tax at the rack (Box 33, Folder 27)
- HB 1277 (00) Free fishing days (Box 33, Folder 28)
- HB 1279 (00) College scholarship assistance act (Box 33, Folder 29)
- HB 1282 (00) Reclamation and reuse of wastewater (Box 33, Folder 30)
- HB 1287 (00) Route 28 transportation improvement district (Box 33, Folder 31)
- HB 1288 (00) Farmer major drought, flood and hurricane disaster act (Box 33, Folder 32)
- HB 1293 (00) Mental health, mental retardation and substance abuse services trust fund (Box 33, Folder 33)
- HB 1295 (00) Records exemptions for certain local housing programs (Box 33, Folder 34)
- HB 1296 (00) Condominium and property owners' association acts; rule violations (Box 33, Folder 35)
- HB 1297 (00) Real estate board; duties (Box 33, Folder 36)
- HB 1299 (00) Motor vehicle, T and M vehicle, trailer, and motorcycle dealers (Box 33, Folder 37)
- HB 1300 (00) Chesapeake bay bridge and tunnel commission (Box 33, Folder 38)
- HB 1303 (00) Summons for unlawful detainer (Box 33, Folder 39)
- HB 1304 (00) Persons with mental retardation, developmental disabilities, etc. (Box 33, Folder 40)
- HB 1305 (00) Marine habitat and waterways improvement fund (Box 33, Folder 41)
- HB 1306 (00) Income tax credits; forested buffers for waterways (Box 33, Folder 42)
- HB 1307 (00) Agricultural stewardship act (Box 33, Folder 43)
- HB 1308 (00) Educational institutions; Gunston Hall and Frontier culture museum (Box 33, Folder 44)
- HB 1312 (00) Court-appointed counsel (Box 33, Folder 45)
- HB 1315 (00) Residential landlord and tenant act (Box 33, Folder 46)
- HB 1316 (00) Manufactured lot rental act; security deposits (Box 33, Folder 47)
- HB 1321 (00) Specialized transportation council (Box 33, Folder 48)
- HB 1324 (00) Open-space lands preservation trust fund (Box 33, Folder 49)
- HB 1326 (00) Conservation easements (Box 33, Folder 50)
- HB 1327 (00) FOIA; records exempt for human rights councils (Box 33, Folder 51)
- HB 1337 (00) Election recounts and contests (Box 33, Folder 52)
- HB 1338 (00) Disasters; joint action by political subdivisions (Box 33, Folder 53)
- HB 1339 (00) Unemployment compensation; definition of employment (Box 33, Folder 54)
- HB 1340 (00) Workforce development training fund (Box 33, Folder 53)
- HB 1341 (00) Powers and duties of the board of pharmacy (Box 33, Folder 56)
- HB 1342 (00) Residential landlord and tenant act; security deposits (Box 33, Folder 57)
- HB 1343 (00) Residential landlord and tenant act; definitions (Box 33, Folder 58)
- HB 1344 (00) Child day programs exempt from licensure (Box 33, Folder 59)
- HB 1345 (00) Overweight vehicles; concrete haulers (Box 33, Folder 60)
- HB 1348 (00) Persons with mental retardation, developmental disabilities, etc. (Box 33, Folder 61)
- HB 1350 (00) Persons with mental retardation, developmental disabilities, etc. (Box 33, Folder 62)
- HB 1352 (00) Emergency services and disaster law (Box 33, Folder 63)
- HB 1353 (00) Remediation programs (Box 33, Folder 64)
- HB 1355 (00) Innovative remedial education pilot program (Box 33, Folder 65)
- HB 1356 (00) Conveyance of land by VDOT (Box 33, Folder 66)
- HB 1359 (00) Child protective services; pilot multiple response system (Box 33, Folder 67)
- HB 1360 (00) Child protective services; statewide differential response system (Box 33, Folder 68)
- HB 1361 (00) Reports of certain offenses to school authorities (Box 33, Folder 69)
- HB 1362 (00) Attorney general; prosecution of criminal cases (Box 33, Folder 70)
- HB 1366 (00) Health insurance; provider panels (Box 33, Folder 71)
- HB 1367 (00) Health care decisions (Box 33, Folder 72)
- HB 1368 (00) Long-term care nursing scholarship and loan repayment program (Box 33, Folder 73)
- HB 1371 (00) Special license plates; class-J no. 611 steam locomotive (Box 33, Folder 74)
- HB 1372 (00) Labor; antique and model boilers (Box 33, Folder 75)
- HB 1375 (00) One-trip vehicle transportation permits (Box 33, Folder 76)
- HB 1376 (00) Accident and sickness insurance; diabetes coverage (Box 33, Folder 77)
- HB 1377 (00) Public utilities; termination of power supply to sewerage systems (Box 33, Folder 78)
- HB 1383 (00) Economic and employment improvement program for disadvantaged (Box 33, Folder 79)
- HB 1385 (00) Sale of certain property in the city of Richmond (Box 33, Folder 80)
- HB 1387 (00) Illegal sales of cigarettes (Box 33, Folder 81)
- HB 1391 (00) Professional use of prescriptions (Box 33, Folder 82)
- HB 1392 (00) Attorney general; review disposition of assets of nonprofit entities (Box 33, Folder 83)
- HB 1395 (00) Review by workers' compensation commission (Box 33, Folder 84)
- HB 1397 (00) Compensation of victims of crime (Box 33, Folder 85)
- HB 1399 (00) Fire protection or emergency medical services by a for profit entity (Box 33, Folder 86)
- HB 1404 (00) Teaching scholarship loan program (Box 33, Folder 87)
- HB 1405 (00) Medical assistance services; coverage (Box 33, Folder 88)
- HB 1406 (00) Gifted education pilot program (Box 33, Folder 89)
- HB 1408 (00) Scholarship for teachers program and fund (Box 33, Folder 90)
- HB 1409 (00) Highway matching funds; utilities (Box 33, Folder 91)
- HB 1411 (00) Transportation district commission of Hampton Roads (Box 33, Folder 92)
- HB 1414 (00) Voter registration procedures for presidential and federal elections (Box 33, Folder 93)
- HB 1420 (00) Workers' compensation; medical reports (Box 33, Folder 94)
- HB 1421 (00) Special license plates; fraternal order of police (Box 33, Folder 95)
- HB 1422 (00) Special license plates; US submarine force centennial (Box 33, Folder 96)
- HB 1424 (00) Rappahannock river basin commission (Box 33, Folder 97)
- HB 1427 (00) Certified interior designers (Box 33, Folder 98)
- HB 1428 (00) Certified interior designers (Box 33, Folder 99)
- HB 1430 (00) Driver's licenses (Box 33, Folder 100)
- HB 1435 (00) Special license plates; marriage encounter movement (Box 33, Folder 101)
- HB 1436 (00) Learner's permits (Box 33, Folder 102)
- HB 1437 (00) Health professions; pharmacy (Box 33, Folder 103)
- HB 1438 (00) Preschool physical examinations (Box 33, Folder 104)
- HB 1439 (00) Mineral mine safety act; annual reports (Box 33, Folder 105)
- HB 1440 (00) Procurement act; electronic posting of public notices, 106 (Box 33)
- HB 1444 (00) Personal property; motor vehicles owned or leased by churches (Box 33, Folder 107)
- HB 1445 (00) Student searches (Box 33, Folder 108)
- HB 1454 (00) Boards of zoning appeals (Box 34, Folder 1)
- HB 1455 (00) ABC; hearings by ABC Board (Box 34, Folder 2)
- HB 1456 (00) Zoning ordinances; restrictions on ABC licenses (Box 34, Folder 3)
- HB 1457 (00) Special license plates; registered nurses (Box 34, Folder 4)
- HB 1458 (00 Health insurance; long-term care insurance for local employees (Box 34, Folder 5)
- HB 1459 (00 Elections; activities at Polling Places; election pages (Box 34, Folder 6)
- HB 1461 (00) Sale, distribution or possession of bidis (Box 34, Folder 7)
- HB 1463 (00) Board of visitors for Mount Vernon (Box 34, Folder 8)
- HB 1464 (00) Employment training and unemployment compensation (Box 34, Folder 9)
- HB 1465 (00) Driver's license endorsements, classifications, and restrictions (Box 34, Folder 10)
- HB 1466 (00) Parking (Box 34, Folder 11)
- HB 1468 (00) Compulsory school attendance (Box 34, Folder 12)
- HB 1469 (00) Health professions; board of physical therapy (Box 34, Folder 13)
- HB 1471 (00) Medical College of Virginia hospitals authority (Box 34, Folder 14)
- HB 1474 (00) Regional economic development authority (Box 34, Folder 15)
- HB 1477 (00) Renal dialysis treatment (Box 34, Folder 16)
- HB 1481 (00) Upkeep and maintenance of Virginia War Memorial Carillon (Box 34, Folder 17)
- HB 1484 (00) Standards of learning assessments (Box 34, Folder 18)
- HB 1486 (00) Redistricting and precinct changes; use of U.S. Census population count (Box 34, Folder 19)
- HB 1487 (00) Health; inspections (Box 34, Folder 20)
- HB 1488 (00) Health; mammograms (Box 32, Folder 21)
- HB 1489 (00) Health insurance for children (Box 32, Folder 22)
- HB 1492 (00) Unlawful electronic file or mail (Box 34, Folder 23)
- HB 1494 (00) BPOL tax; related entity exclusion (Box 32, Folder 24)
- HB 1497 (00) Accident and sickness insurance; notice of priority of benefits (Box 34, Folder 25)
- HB 1498 (00) Child's records (Box 34, Folder 26)
- HB 1499 (00) School Records as evidence (Box 32, Folder 27)
- HB 1503 (00) Tenants by the entireties; revocable trust (Box 34, Folder 28)
- HB 1510 (00) Comprehensive services act for at-risk youth and families (Box 34, Folder 29)
- HB 1511 (00) Long-term care insurance (Box 34, Folder 30)
- HB 1514 (00) Animal pounds (Box 34, Folder 31)
- HB 1516 (00) Special license plates; retired state employees (Box 34, Folder 32)
- HB 1517 (00) Planning time for teachers (Box 34, Folder 33)
- HB 1518 (00) Procedures in election recounts (Box 34, Folder 34)
- HB 1520 (00) Disability; developmental disability (Box 34, Folder 35)
- HB 1522 (00) Emissions inspections (Box 34, Folder 36)
- HB 1524 (00) Harassment by computer (Box 34, Folder 37)
- HB 1525 (00) Emergency medical services vehicles (Box 34, Folder 38)
- HB 1528 (00) Advantage Virginia incentive program (Box 34, Folder 39)
- HB 1533 (00) Bail and recognizance (Box 34, Folder 40)
- HB 1535 (00) Town of Irvington; council elections (Box 34, Folder 41)
- HB 1536 (00) Primary schedule in 2001 (Box 34, Folder 42)
- HB 1537 (00) Special elections; vacancies in constitutional offices (Box 34, Folder 43)
- HB 1539 (00) Blue Ridge hospital; conveyance (Box 34, Folder 44)
- HB 1540 (00) Racing commission (Box 34, Folder 45)
- HB 1541 (00) School board policies prohibiting certain activities (Box 34, Folder 46)
- HB 1546 (00) Liability of landlord; lead-based paint (Box 34, Folder 47)
- HB 1547 (00) Civil remedies; appeal bond (Box 34, Folder 48)
- HB 1548 (00) University of Virginia; endowment funds (Box 34, Folder 49)
- HB 1552 (00) Patrick Hospital authority (Box 34, Folder 50)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 1-50 (Box 34, Folder 51)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 51-100 (Box 34, Folder 52)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 101-150 (Box 34, Folder 53)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 151-200 (Box 34, Folder 54)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 201-250 (Box 34, Folder 55)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 251-350 (Box 34, Folder 56)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 351-399 (Box 34, Folder 57)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 400-450 (Box 34, Folder 58)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 451-500 (Box 34, Folder 59)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 501-550 (Box 34, Folder 60)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 551-599 (Box 34, Folder 61)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 600-650 (Box 34, Folder 62)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 651-679 (Box 34, Folder 63)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 680-699 (Box 34, Folder 64)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 700-725 (Box 34, Folder 65)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 726-750 (Box 34, Folder 66)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 751-799 (Box 34, Folder 67)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 800-849 (Box 34, Folder 68)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 850-899 (Box 34, Folder 69)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 900-930 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 931-949 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 950-979 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 980-999 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 1000-1029 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- 2000 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 1030-1071 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- SB 252 (01) Sentencing for Class 1 Misdemeanors (Box 36, Folder 1)
- SB 291 (01) Joseph V. Gartlan, Jr. Parkway (Box 36, Folder 2)
- SB 462 (01) Uniform Child Custody Jurisdiction and Enforcement Act; created (Box 36, Folder 3)
- SB 646 (01) Information on Proposed Constitutional Amendments (Box 36, Folder 4)
- SB 694 (01) Special Grand Juries (Box 36, Folder 5)
- SB 724 (01) Family Access to Medical Insurance Security (FAMIS) Plan (Box 36, Folder 6)